

Md. Rohul Amin

Software Engineer

- Sha 66/3, Shadhinata Sarani, North Badda, Gulshan, Dhaka, Bangladesh ## 05 Jan 1996
- Bangladeshi @ Unmarried in radipu radipu radipu radipu
 ★ radipu.me radipu

CAREER OBJECTIVES

I am a graduate with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Engineering. I am experienced in leadership and both front-end and back-end programming languages. Now, I am looking for establishing my career as a .NET developer and team lead. I am a quick learner and willing to learn new technologies to upgrade myself with time. I am working with .NET technology since 2018.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jan 2022

Software Engineer

Dhaka, Bangladesh

CureTech Ltd 🛮

- Developed web applications.
- Worked on the Engineering part for different projects.
- · Lead a team.
- I worked here with C# .NET5, Angular, NodeJS, MSSQL, Laravel, MySQL, AWS, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Software Design

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

Software Engineer

Sunderland, England

Ginilab Limited

- Worked on Restaurant Management System.
- · Added new features, and debugging.
- I worked there with .NET Framework, DevExpress, WinForms, Software Design, Fron-end, and Back-end.

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

Software Engineer

Dhaka, Bangladesh

OurEdu

- Worked on Account Management System.
- · Upgrading the old technology to new technology.
- I have had working here with C# ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, LINQ, CSS, MSSQL, and DevOps.

Jan 2015 - Jan 2021

Head of Information and Communication Technology

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Bangladesh Study Forum (BDSF)

- I developed the whole IT system for this organization.
- Lead the IT team
- What have I done: Website development, Organized programs, public speaking, Leadership.

PROJECTS

Feb 2022 - present

Bachao 🛮

Against the rape

- It's a mobile application platform against rape.
- The backend was developed with .NET.
- Technology Used: .NET5, Angular, WebAPI, MSSQL

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

Restaurant Management System

- It's a desktop software, mostly used in the UK and in the middle east.
- Nearly 200+ restaurants and thousands of customers use this software for ordering food inside and outside the restaurant.
- Technology Used: ASP.NET, DevExpress, WinForms, MySQL, Laragon, HeidiSQL

Feb 2021 - May 2021

Account Management System for Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

- Enroll new students with details information.
- · Adding new staff and teachers.
- Payroll and tuition fees management.
- Online payment module.
- Technology Used: C#, ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ, and following Onion Architecture.

May 2019 - Aug 2019

Library Management System

Technology Used: C#, ASP.NET Core 2.1, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ.

SKILLS

Programming Language

C, C++, Java, JavaScript, C#, R, Python, TypeScript, Go

Backend Development

.NET Core, .NET, NodeJS, Laravel

DevOps

AWS, GCP, Azure, Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes, Bash

Data Structure and -**Algorithm**

Cyber Security Penetration, Forensics, Reverse Engineering, Social Engineering

Frontend

Development

VueJS, Angular, HTML5, AngularJS, Bootstrap3, 4, CSS3, Sass

Database

Oracle, MySQL, MSSQL Server, PostgreSQL

Source Control

Git. GitHub

Interpersonal skills —

Listening, Caring, Leadership, Self-Motivated, Responsibility, Teamwork

EDUCATION

May 2021 Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

International University of Business Agriculture and Technology Dhaka, Bangladesh

Completed BSc with a CGPA of 3.27 out of 4.00

Jul 2011 - Aug 2013 **Higher Secondary Certificate**

Dhaka, Bangladesh Cambrian College

Completed HSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

Secondary School Certificate Jan 2009 - May 2011 Cumilla, Bangladesh Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

Completed SSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

INTERESTS

 Learning New Skills Public Speaking

Reading

 Leadership Writing

LANGUAGES

Bangla **English**